(Leonard:)...but it turns out
he's a black-diamond skier...
(Leonard:)...he collects vintage motorcycles,
he plays in a rock band.
- So? We're in a rock band.
- No.
We play "Rock Band" on our Xbox.
(Sheldon:)Nice motivational speech
from our lead guitarist.
(Leonard:)He's funny too.
(Leonard:)He does this hysterical impersonation
of Stephen Hawking having phone sex.
[AS STEPHEN HAWKING]
What are you wearing?
[IN NORMAL VOICE]
That's not... He does it better.
(Leonard:)He said he was gonna take me to the gym
so I'm gonna go practice my sit-ups.
Wow. Humongous man crush, dude.
Yup, it's officially a bromance.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
(Penny(entering):)Hey, Sheldon. Are you and Leonard
putting up a Christmas tree?
(Sheldon:)No, because we don't celebrate
the ancient pagan festival of Saturnalia.
(Penny:)Saturnalia?
Gather around, kids. It's time for Sheldon's
beloved Christmas special.